A Guide to the Harry F. Byrd Jr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Legislative Files
  - Subseries A: General
    - Agency for International Development, 1966-1970; (2 folders) (Box Box 62)
    - Agriculture, 1970 Feb-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 62)
    - Agriculture, 1968-1970 Jan; (7 folders) (Box Box 63)
    - Agriculture, 1965-1967; (5 folders) (Box Box 64)
    - Agriculture: Apples, Burley Tobacco, Cherries, & Cotton, 1967-1972 (Box Box 64)
    - Agriculture: Business & Imports, 1968-1972 (Box Box 64)
    - Agriculture: Crop Insurance, Drought Disaster, 1966, 1971 (Box Box 64)
    - Agriculture: Davidson, Gordon, Sr., Case of, 1958-1967 (Box Box 65)
    - Agriculture: Evaporated Milk, 1968 (Box Box 65)
    - Agriculture: Farmers' Home Administration, 1967-1972; (4 folders) (Box Box 65)
    - Agriculture: Farmers' Home Administration, 1965-1966 (Box Box 66)
    - Agriculture: Fish, 1971-1972 (Box Box 66)
    - Agriculture: Food Stamp Program & Abuses, 1968-1972, n.d.; (4 folders) (Box Box 66)
    - Agriculture: Honeybees, 1970 (Box Box 66)
    - Agriculture: International Grain Arrangements, 1968 (Box Box 66)
    - Agriculture: International Trade, 1971 (Box Box 66)
    - Agriculture: Legislation, 1971 Mar-1972 Jun; (2 folders) (Box Box 66)
    - Agriculture: Legislation, 1967 Jun-1970 Dec; (6 folders) (Box Box 67)
    - Agriculture: Legislation, 1966-1967 May; (3 folders) (Box Box 68)
    - Agriculture: Legislation - Testimony, 1968; (2 folders) (Box Box 68)
    - Agriculture: Meat, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 68)
    - Agriculture: Milk and Dairy, 1968-1972 (Box Box 69)
    - Agriculture: Peanuts, 1966-1972; (4 folders) (Box Box 69)
    - Agriculture: Peanut Disaster, 1969-1972 (Box Box 69)
    - Agriculture: Potatoes, 1968, 1972 (Box Box 69)
    - Agriculture: Poultry and Eggs, 1966-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 70)
    - Agriculture: Resource Conservation and Development Project Plan, 1966 (Box Box 70)
    - Agriculture: Rural Development Act, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 71)
    - Agriculture: School Lunch Program, 1968-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 71)
    - Agriculture Secretary Nomination: Butz, Earl L., 1971 (Box Box 71)
    - Agriculture: Soil and Water Conservation & Forestry, 1968-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 71)
    - Agriculture: Soil and Water Conservation & Forestry - Crabtree Falls, 1969 (Box Box 71)
    - Agriculture: Tobacco, 1967-1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 72)
    - Agriculture: Unions, 1967-1971 (Box Box 72)
    - Air Force, 1970-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 72)
    - Air Force, 1965-1967 (Box Box 73)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, 1969 (Box Box 73)
    - Americans for Constitutional Action, 1966-1969 (Box Box 73)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1967-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 73)
    - Apportionment, 1966 (Box Box 73)
    - Appropriations, 1972 May-Dec; (3 folders) (Box Box 73)
    - Appropriations, 1971 May-1972 Apr; (7 folders) (Box Box 74)
    - Appropriations, 1967 Aug-1971 Apr; (7 folders) (Box Box 75)
    - Appropriations, 1966 Aug-1967 Aug; (7 folders) (Box Box 76)
    - Appropriations, 1966 Mar-Aug; (3 folders) (Box Box 77)
    - Appropriations: Anti-Poverty Program - Big Stone Gap Petitions, 1967 (Box Box 77)
    - Appropriations: Schools, 1966-1967 (Box Box 77)
    - Arab-Israeli Conflict, 1967 Jun-Aug; (3 folders) (Box Box 77)
    - Arab-Israeli Conflict, 1967 May; (2 folders) (Box Box 78)
    - Army, 1971 Sep-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 78)
    - Army, 1970 Oct-1971 Aug; (6 folders) (Box Box 79)
    - Army, 1969-1970 Sep; (7 folders) (Box Box 80)
    - Army, 1967 Aug-1968; (7 folders) (Box Box 81)
    - Army, 1965 Nov-1967 Jul; (7 folders) (Box Box 82)
    - Army: Arlington National Cemetery, 1967-1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 83)
    - Army: Corps of Engineers, 1971 Aug-1973; (5 folders) (Box Box 83)
    - Army: Corps of Engineers, 1968-1971 Jul; (8 folders) (Box Box 84)
    - Army: Corps of Engineers, 1965-1967 (Box Box 85)
    - Army: Corps of Engineers - Big Caney Water System, 1967 (Box Box 85)
    - Army: Corps of Engineers - Chincoteague Inlet, 1970 (Box Box 85)
    - Army: Corps of Engineers - Delmarva Intracoastal Waterway, 1969 (Box Box 85)
    - Army: Corps of Engineers - The Elizabeth River, 1970-1972 (Box Box 85)
    - Army: T.M.C. Systems and Power Corporation, 1969 (Box Box 85)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 85)
    - Automobile Industry: No-Fault Insurance, 1972 (Box Box 85)
    - Automobile Industry: Odometer Bill, ca. 1969 (Box Box 85)
    - Banking & Currency: Bank-Holding Company Bill, 1970; (3 folders) (Box Box 86)
    - Banking & Currency: Banking Reform, 1971-1972 (Box Box 86)
    - Banking & Currency: Participation Sales Act of 1966 (Box Box 86)
    - Census Bureau, 1970-1971, 1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 86)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1966-1969 (Box Box 86)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1970-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 86)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1965-1969; (3 folders) (Box Box 87)
    - Civil Rights, 1967 Aug 7-Dec; (5 folders) (Box Box 87)
    - Civil Rights, 1967 Jan-Aug 4; (8 folders) (Box Box 88)
    - Civil Rights, 1966 Mar-Dec; (7 folders) (Box Box 89)
    - Civil Service, 1965-1971, 1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 90)
    - Coal Mining, 1971-1972 (Box Box 90)
    - Commerce, Dept. of, 1968-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 90)
    - Commerce, Dept. of, 1965-1967; (3 folders) (Box Box 91)
    - Commerce: Communications, 1974 (Box Box 91)
    - Commerce: Communications - Radio, 1973-1974 (Box Box 91)
    - Commerce: Communications - TV, 1974 (Box Box 91)
    - Commerce: Consumer Affairs, 1968-1971 (Box Box 91)
    - Commerce: Consumer Fair Trade Practices, 1974 (Box Box 91)
    - Commerce: Consumer Protection & Complaints, 1974 Oct-Dec; (2 folders) (Box Box 91)
    - Commerce: Consumer Protection & Complaints, 1974 Jan-Sep; (7 folders) (Box Box 92)
    - Commerce: Cumberlands Airport Commission, 1970 (Box Box 93)
    - Commerce: Dulles National Airport Bill, 1967-1969 (Box Box 93)
    - Commerce: Fair Packaging & Labeling, 1966-1974 (Box Box 93)
    - Commerce: Foreign Exports - Grain, Oil, Hides, Etc., 1966, 1974 (Box Box 93)
    - Commerce: Foreign Imports, 1974 (Box Box 93)
    - Commerce: Foreign Investments, 1974 (Box Box 93)
    - Commerce: Missile Device Sale to Poland, 1967; (3 folders) (Box Box 93)
    - Commerce: Trade Reform Bill, 1974; (5 folders) (Box Box 94)
    - Congressional Four Year Term Proposal, 1966 (Box Box 94)
    - Congressional Redistricting, 1967 (Box Box 94)
    - Crime Bill, 1969-1970, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 94)
    - Debt Ceiling Amendment, 1967, 1969 (Box Box 95)
    - Defense, Dept. of, 1969 May-1972 Jun; (5 folders) (Box Box 95)
    - Defense, Dept. of, 1967-1969 Apr; (7 folders) (Box Box 96)
    - Defense, Dept. of, 1965-1966; (3 folders) (Box Box 97)
    - Defense, Dept. of: Defense Supply Agency, 1969 (Box Box 97)
    - Defense, Dept. of: Milk Procurement, 1965-1967 (Box Box 97)
    - Disaster Relief, 1969 & 1972 (Box Box 97)
    - District of Columbia, 1970-1972 (Box Box 97)
    - District of Columbia, 1966-1969; (4 folders) (Box Box 98)
    - District of Columbia: Convention Center-Sports Arena, 1971 (Box Box 98)
    - District of Columbia: Policemen & Firemen, 1971-1972 (Box Box 98)
    - District of Columbia, Maryland, & Virginia School Merger Proposal, 1966 (Box Box 98)
    - Drug Abuse Prevention, 1972 (Box Box 98)
    - East-West Trade, 1967; (2 folders) (Box Box 99)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1966-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 99)
    - Economic Development Administration: Alberta, Virginia, 1970 (Box Box 100)
    - Economic Development Administration: Appalachian Regional Hospitals, 1969, 1972 (Box Box 100)
    - Economic Development Administration: Cedar Island Bridge and Beach Authority, 1966 (Box Box 100)
    - Economic Development Administration: Cumberland Plateau, 1971-1972 (Box Box 100)
    - Economic Stabilization Program: Phase II, 1971 (Box Box 100)
    - Economic Stabilization Program: Wage-Price Freeze, 1971-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 100)
    - Education, 1968-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 101)
    - Education: Allen, Dr. James E., 1965-1969 (Box Box 101)
    - Education: Busing, 1972 (Box Box 101)
    - Education: Higher Education Act, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 102)
    - Education: Impact Aid Program, 1968-1972 (Box Box 102)
    - Education: Student Loans, 1972 (Box Box 102)
    - Education: Vocational Rehabilitation and Employment of the Handicapped, 1971-1972 (Box Box 102)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1971-1972; (4 folders) (Box Box 102)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 103)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1966 (Box Box 103)
    - Export-Import Bank of the United States, 1967-1972 (Box Box 103)
    - Export-Import Bank Bill, 1967; (4 folders) (Box Box 103)
    - Federal Agencies Grants, 1965-1966 (Box Box 104)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1968 Jun-1972; (6 folders) (Box Box 104)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1965-1967; (3 folders) (Box Box 105)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Fairfax County Airpark, 1963-1966 (Box Box 105)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Lonesome Pine Airport, 1967-1969 (Box Box 105)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Restricted Air Traffic, 1968-1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 105)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Richmond Airport Service, 1969-1970 (Box Box 106)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Users Charge, 1967 (Box Box 106)
    - Federal Budget, 1967-1969 (Box Box 106)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1967 Oct-1972, 1974; (5 folders) (Box Box 106)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1965-1967 Sep; (3 folders) (Box Box 107)
    - Federal Credit Union Bill (H.R. 9961), 1971 (Box Box 107)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1968-1969 (Box Box 107)
    - Federal Highway Commission, 1965 (Box Box 107)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1966-1972 (Box Box 107)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1965-1967 (Box Box 107)
    - Federal Power Commission, 1971-1973 (Box Box 107)
    - Federal Power Commission, 1965-1970; (3 folders) (Box Box 108)
    - Federal Power Commission: Blue Ridge Dam Project, 1966-1970; (5 folders) (Box Box 108)
    - Federal Power Commission: Vepco Dam, 1969 (Box Box 109)
    - Federal Reserve System, 1965-1972 (Box Box 109)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1969 Jul-1972, 1974; (6 folders) (Box Box 109)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1966-1969 Jun; (2 folders) (Box Box 110)
    - Federal Trade Commission: Georgia-Pacific Corporation, 1971 (Box Box 110)
    - Federal Water Quality Administration, 1970 (Box Box 110)
    - Federal Water Quality Administration: Clintwood, Virginia, 1970 (Box Box 110)
    - Filibuster Rule XXII, 1967 (Box Box 110)
    - Fiscal Issues, 1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 110)
    - Fiscal Issues, 1968; (8 folders) (Box Box 111)
    - Fiscal Issues, 1966 Apr-1967; (7 folders) (Box Box 112)
    - Fiscal Issues, 1965-1966 Mar (Box Box 113)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1972 (Box Box 113)
    - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1968 (Box Box 113)
    - France, 1967 (Box Box 113)
    - General Accounting Office, 1969-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 113)
    - General Services Administration, 1970-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 113)
    - General Services Administration, 1965-1969; (3 folders) (Box Box 114)
    - Government Printing Office, 1969-1971 (Box Box 114)
    - Greece, 1969-1971 (Box Box 114)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1972 Sep-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 114)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1971 Jul-1972 Aug; (7 folders) (Box Box 115)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1970 Jul-1971 Jun; (7 folders) (Box Box 116)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1969 Jul-1970 Jun; (7 folders) (Box Box 117)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1968 Oct-1969 Jun; (6 folders) (Box Box 118)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1966 Aug-1968 Oct; (7 folders) (Box Box 119)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1965-1966 Jul; (3 folders) (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Accomack County Schools, 1970-1971 (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Aging, 1971-1972 (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Albemarle County Busing, 1971 (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Black and Brown Lung Legislation, 1970-1972 (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Blue Cross and Blue Shield, 1971-1972 (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Campbell County Schools, 1972 (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Catastrophic Illness Insurance, 1971 (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Charlottesville Facilities, 1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 120)
    - HEW: Dinwiddie County School Integration, 1967-1969 (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Harrisonburg Medicare Office, 1969 (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Health Manpower Training, 1970-1972 (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Hill-Burton Charity Care, 1970, 1972-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Hospitals and the National Labor Relations Act, 1972 (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Isle of Wight and Amherst School Aid Funds, 1971 (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Lee County Medical Health Center, 1968-1969 (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Manpower Administration and Psychological Training, 1971-1972 (Box Box 121)
    - HEW: Marymount College, 1968 (Box Box 122)
    - HEW: Medicare, 1966-1972; (4 folders) (Box Box 122)
    - HEW: Medicredit, 1970-1972 (Box Box 122)
    - HEW: Mental Health, 1972 (Box Box 122)
    - HEW: Migrant Health Program, 1972 (Box Box 122)
    - HEW: Nansemond County Schools, 1971 (Box Box 122)
    - HEW: National Health Insurance, 1970-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Newport News Schools, 1968 (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Norfolk City Schools, 1971 (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Population Control, 1971 (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Public Health, 1970-1972 (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Rural Medicine, 1970-1972 (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Schools, 1969 (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Severinson, Dr. Eloise& Virginia Education, 1971-1972 (Box Box 123)
    - HEW: Vitamins, 1966 (Box Box 123)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1970 Jul-1972; (6 folders) (Box Box 124)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1965-1970 Jul; (5 folders) (Box Box 125)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Hopewell and Petersburg Water & Sewer Projects, 1970 (Box Box 125)
    - HUD: Real Estate Attorney Fees, 1972 Aug 22-Nov; (2 folders) (Box Box 125)
    - HUD: Real Estate Attorney Fees, 1972 Feb-Aug 18; (2 folders) (Box Box 126)
    - HUD: Virginia Beach, 1968, 1970 (Box Box 126)
    - HUD: Wise County, 1971 (Box Box 126)
    - Humanities, 1965-1966 (Box Box 126)
    - Hurricanes and Floods, 1969-1970; (4 folders) (Box Box 126)
    - Imex Corporation Proposal, 1971 (Box Box 127)
    - Immigration, 1968 May-1972; (7 folders) (Box Box 127)
    - Immigration, 1964-1968 Apr; (4 folders) (Box Box 128)
    - Indian Education, 1971-1972 (Box Box 128)
    - Inflation, 1970-1972 (Box Box 128)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1972 Mar-1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 128)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1970 Oct-1972 Feb; (7 folders) (Box Box 129)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1969-1970 Sep; (7 folders) (Box Box 130)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1967-1968; (7 folders) (Box Box 131)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1965-1966; (3 folders) (Box Box 132)
    - Interior, Dept. of: Back Bay National Wildlife Refuge, 1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 132)
    - Interior, Dept. of: Madison County, Virginia Land Exchange, 1968 (Box Box 132)
    - Interior, Dept. of: Redwood National Park, 1967 (Box Box 132)
    - Interior, Dept. of: Richmond Regional Office, 1971 (Box Box 132)
    - Internal Revenue, 1967-1972; (7 folders) (Box Box 133)
    - Internal Revenue, 1964-1966; (3 folders) (Box Box 134)
    - Internal Revenue: Pensions, Annuities, Profit Sharing, etc., 1966 (Box Box 134)
    - Internal Revenue: School Tax Rulings, 1966-1972 (Box Box 134)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 134)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1966-1970; (5 folders) (Box Box 135)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission: Railroad Boxcars, 1966 (Box Box 135)
    - Investment Tax Credit, 1966 (Box Box 135)
    - Judges, Federal: Constitutional Amendment, 1971-1972; (7 folders) (Box Box 136)
    - Justice, Dept. of, 1972 (Box Box 136)
    - Justice, Dept. of, 1965-1971; (7 folders) (Box Box 137)
    - Justice, Dept. of: Carmichael, Stokely, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box Box 138)
    - Justice, Dept. of: Correspondence with Prisoners, 1971-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 138)
    - Labor, Dept. of, 1971 Oct-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 138)
    - Labor, Dept. of, 1968-1971 Sep; (7 folders) (Box Box 139)
    - Labor, Dept. of, 1965-1967; (3 folders) (Box Box 140)
    - Labor, Dept. of: Labor (HEW) Appropriations Bill, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 140)
    - Labor, Dept. of: Manpower Training and Employment Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box Box 140)
    - Labor, Dept. of: Minimum Wage, 1971 (Box Box 140)
    - Labor, Dept. of: Scott County, 1969-1970 (Box Box 140)
    - Labor Legislation, 1971 Feb-1973 Jan; (6 folders) (Box Box 141)
    - Labor Legislation, 1966 Sep-1967; (7 folders) (Box Box 142)
    - Labor Legislation, 1966 Mar-Aug; (7 folders) (Box Box 143)
    - Labor Legislation, 1966 Jan 24-Feb; (6 folders) (Box Box 144)
    - Labor Legislation, 1965-1966 Jan 21; (3 folders) (Box Box 145)
    - Lee, R.E.: Citizenship Rights, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 145)
    - Library of Congress, 1965-1967, 1969-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 145)
    - Marine Mammal Protection Act, 1972 (Box Box 146)
    - Maritime Administration, 1965-1966 (Box Box 146)
    - Mass Transit, 1966, 1968 (Box Box 146)
    - Military Justice Act of 1971 (Box Box 146)
    - Mining Legislation, 1966, 1969-1971; (3 folders) (Box Box 146)
    - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1966-1972 (Box Box 146)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1967-1972 (Box Box 146)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1971-1972 (Box Box 146)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1965-1970; (2 folders) (Box Box 147)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration: Lab at William and Mary, 1971 (Box Box 147)
    - National Archives, 1971 (Box Box 147)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1972 (Box Box 147)
    - National Capital Housing Authority, 1968-1969 (Box Box 147)
    - National Capital Planning Commission, 1969 (Box Box 147)
    - National Endowment for the Arts & Humanities, 1969-1972 (Box Box 147)
    - National Guard, 1971-1972 (Box Box 147)
    - National Guard: Armory at Suffolk, 1968 (Box Box 147)
    - National Recreation and Park Association, 1968 (Box Box 147)
    - National Science Foundation, 1968-1972 (Box Box 147)
    - Natural Gas Legislation, 1971 (Box Box 147)
    - Natural Resources: Coal Mine Health & Safety Act of 1969 (Box Box 147)
    - Natural Resources: Coal Mine Strike, 1969-1970; (2 folders) (Box Box 147)
    - Natural Resources: Coal Testimony, 1969-1971, N.D.; (2 folders) (Box Box 148)
    - Natural Resources: Mobjack Bay Development Corporation, 1968-1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 148)
    - Navy, 1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 148)
    - Navy, 1970-1971; (6 folders) (Box Box 149)
    - Navy, 1968 May-1969; (7 folders) (Box Box 150)
    - Navy, 1966-1968 Apr; (7 folders) (Box Box 151)
    - Navy, 1965 (Box Box 152)
    - Navy-Marine-Coast Guard Residence Foundation, 1971 (Box Box 152)
    - Norfolk Naval Shipyard and Civilian Wages, 1972 (Box Box 152)
    - Occupational Health & Safety Legislation, 1969-1972 (Box Box 152)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1969-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 152)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1965-1967, n.d.; (5 folders) (Box Box 153)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity: Central Virginia Health Clinic, 1970 (Box Box 153)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity: Shriver, Sargent, 1967-1968 (Box Box 153)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity: Total Action Against Poverty, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box Box 153)
    - Office of Management & Budget, 1971 (Box Box 153)
    - Page Employment in the Senate, 1971-1972 (Box Box 154)
    - Panama Canal Treaty, 1967; (4 folders) (Box Box 154)
    - Parcel Post Legislation: Favorable, 1966 (Box Box 154)
    - Parcel Post Legislation: Unfavorable, 1966 (Box Box 155)
    - Patent Office, 1962-1967; (2 folders) (Box Box 155)
    - Patents: McClellan Bill (S. 644), 1972 (Box Box 155)
    - Patriotism, 1967 (Box Box 155)
    - Peace Corps, 1968 (Box Box 155)
    - Pesticide Legislation, 1972 (Box Box 155)
    - Piney Point, Maryland Oil Distillation Plant, 1969; (3 folders) (Box Box 155)
    - Post Office, 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 155)
    - Post Office, 1969 Apr-1970 Nov; (7 folders) (Box Box 156)
    - Post Office, 1965-1967, 1969 Jan-Mar; (5 folders) (Box Box 157)
    - Post Office: Commemorative Stamp - Harry F. Byrd, Sr., 1968 (Box Box 157)
    - Post Office: Commemorative Stamp - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1966 (Box Box 157)
    - Post Office: Commemorative Stamp - Jack Jouett, 1968 (Box Box 157)
    - Post Office: Commemorative Stamp - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, 1967 (Box Box 158)
    - Post Office: Commemorative Stamp Requests, 1964-1967 (Box Box 158)
    - Post Office: Mobile Postal Unit, 1967 (Box Box 158)
    - Postal Reform, 1970 (Box Box 158)
    - Prayer Amendment, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box Box 158)
    - Public Buildings Amendment, 1971 (Box Box 158)
    - Public Utilities, 1971-1972 (Box Box 158)
    - Railroad Retirement Act, 1969-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 158)
    - Rhodesia, 1967; (7 folders) (Box Box 159)
    - Rhodesia, 1966; (2 folders) (Box Box 160)
    - Rhodesia: Chrome, 1971 Oct-1973 Jan; (6 folders) (Box Box 160)
    - Rhodesia: Chrome, 1971 Apr-Sep (Box Box 161)
    - Rural Electrification Administration, 1966-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 161)
    - Safety Legislation, 1972 (Box Box 161)
    - Sargent-at-Arms, 1966-1971; (2 folders) (Box Box 161)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1969-1970 (Box Box 161)
    - Selective Service System, 1967 Jun-1972; (7 folders) (Box Box 162)
    - Selective Service System, 1965-1967 May; (3 folders) (Box Box 163)
    - Senate Committees, 1969 Dec-1972; (4 folders) (Box Box 163)
    - Senate Committees, 1965-1967 Dec; (3 folders) (Box Box 164)
    - Small Business Administration, 1965-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 164)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1968-1972 (Box Box 164)
    - Social Security Amendments, 1970; (3 folders) (Box Box 165)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Charts and Statistics, 1971-1972 (Box Box 165)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Correspondence, 1970-1972, n.d.; (3 folders) (Box Box 165)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box Box 166)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Notes and Memoranda (Box Box 166)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Press Releases and Statements, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 166)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Printed Material, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 166)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Printed Material Generated by the Committee on Finance, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 166)
    - Social Security Amendments of 1972 (H.R. 1): Testimony, 1971-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 167)
    - Social Security Bill (H.R. 5710), 1967 (Box Box 167)
    - Space Treaty, 1967 (Box Box 167)
    - Speakers, 1965-1970; (3 folders) (Box Box 167)
    - Sports Legislation, 1966 (Box Box 168)
    - State Department, 1970 Apr-1973; (6 folders) (Box Box 168)
    - State Department, 1968-1970 Mar; (7 folders) (Box Box 169)
    - State Department, 1967; (6 folders) (Box Box 170)
    - State Department, 1964-1966; (5 folders) (Box Box 171)
    - State Department: Carmichael, Stokely- Passport, 1968-1969 (Box Box 171)
    - State Department: Jewish Emigration, 1969 (Box Box 171)
    - State Department: Ian Smith, 1967-1970 (Box Box 171)
    - State Department: Otepka, Otto, 1965-1969 (Box Box 171)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks, 1972 (Box Box 172)